fantasysharks.com 2003-02-07

# FantasySharks.com Privacy Policy

|   
---  
Message Boards  
What's This?  
Team Links  
Depth Charts  
Schedule Grid  
Weekly Schedules  
Team Schedules  
  
* * *  
  
Fantasy Links  
|  **FantasySharks.com Privacy Policy**  
**Last revised: July 27, 2002**

* * *

FantasySharks.com shares your concern about the protection of your personal information online. This is our policy regarding the privacy of information we collect on our web sites.

**Information Gathered and Tracked by FantasySharks.com, Inc.** **FantasySharks.com, Inc.**

FantasySharks.com, Inc. gathers two types of data about users: (a) personal information, which individual users provide (i) when registering as a member of _FantasySharks.com_ , our free flagship site, and (ii) voluntarily at certain other points, such as contests or surveys; and (b) tracking information, which is automatically collected about all visitors to our sites. 

**Personal Information**  
Personal information is gathered in several places on our web sites. We will always provide a secure area of our sites for you to enter your information, but if you prefer, you may talk offline to a customer service representative and provide the required information over the telephone or via email. 

  * **Registration**  
Currently, we do not require users to become members of FantasySharks.com in order to have access to our free commentary, analysis and news, but if you'd like to receive one or more of our free email newsletters, we require you to register to become a member. In order to register, you'll have to supply us with your email address. 
  * **Message Boards and Chats**  
We provide message boards and chats for discussion of various topics. Although any user of FantasySharks.com may read messages posted to the boards, only FantasySharks.com subscribers are permitted to post on the boards. No additional personal information is required to post on the boards. Please note that information you post to a message board or chat will be available for any user of that service to read, and is no longer private. 
  * **Surveys/Polls**  
At certain times, you may be asked to participate in surveys, which are generally aimed at obtaining general information. Because information obtained in these surveys is connected with individual subscribers and is used internally to better market our services, participation is voluntary. In addition, some columnists will on occasion take polls of their readers. Such polls are solely for the editorial use of the individual columnists, and participation is voluntary. 
  * **Contests and Purchases**  
We sometimes offer contests in which certain personal information is required for registration, for purposes of verifying the entrants' identities and notifying the winners. If the contest is being administered by a third party, this information will be disclosed to that third party. We also require shipping and billing information in order to fulfill online purchases of tangible items, such as books and videos.

**Tracking Information**  
Tracking data consists of both individual and aggregated tracking information and is automatically gathered using "cookies". 

  * **What is a "cookie"?**  
A cookie is a small data file containing information, such as a user's login name, that is written to the user's hard drive by a web server and used to track the pages visited. The individual information gathered in this manner is used for internal purposes only, such as accessing a member's account information. We also use the information on an aggregate basis, to track the readership of stories and analyze traffic patterns on our site. 

You can control your browser's settings regarding cookies by selecting "Internet Options" or "Preferences" in the menu bar of your browser. This will allow you to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or disable cookies altogether. However, because cookies allow you to easily navigate our web sites without having to constantly reenter your User Name and password, we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

  * **Tracking by our Advertisers**  
In addition to cookies placed by FantasySharks.com, advertisers and advertising vendors that serve ads onto our web sites may use their own cookies or other tracking technologies. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any such advertisers and vendors. The privacy policy of FastClick, our primary third-party ad server, can be found [here](http://fastclick.com/about/privacy.html). FastClick collects certain non-personally identifiable information in order to better target advertising to you. If you would like to opt-out, click [here](http://www.fastclick.com/about/opt-out.html), and FastClick will change your cookie to one that does not contain a unique user ID number, which will prevent FastClick from collecting any information from your use of the Internet.

FantasySharks.com, Inc. uses information obtained from its users as stated in this Privacy Policy, and to enhance users' experiences on our sites. As a general rule, we will not disclose any personal information to any third parties, except when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, to protect other users of FantasySharks.com's services, or to respond to an emergency. Tracking information is used to create aggregate reports on user demographics and site traffic patterns and then provided to our advertisers and partners, enabling them to better target their advertisements to our users. None of the information provided to them can be connected to the identities or other personal information of individual users. 

  * **Free Email Bulletins**  
If you're a registered member of FantasySharks.com, we use your email address to send you free email bulletins containing selected stories, market information, advertisements and links to our sites. 
  * **Illegal Activity**  
If you partake, or we reasonably suspect that you are partaking, in any illegal activity, we may disclose your personal information without a subpoena, warrant or other court order to the extent we feel is necessary to cooperate with appropriate authorities. 
  * **Corporate Transfers**  
We reserve the right to transfer any personal information or tracking information that we have collected to a third party in the event that we sell or otherwise transfer substantially all of our assets related to any web site that we own or operate and any product or service that we offer.

FantasySharks.com, Inc. uses reasonable security methods to protect the data that resides on our servers. However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our servers, nor can we guarantee that information that users supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. 

**********

Questions regarding this policy should be directed to at [privacy@FantasySharks.com](mailto:privacy@fantasysharks.com). FantasySharks.com reserves the right to modify this policy effective seven (7) days after the posting of the revised policy.

| |
